<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>elasticsearch on ByteBuilders Blog</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/tags/elasticsearch/</link><description>Recent content in elasticsearch on ByteBuilders Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.byte.builders/tags/elasticsearch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AppsCode introduces KubeDB Enterprise - An Enterprise-grade Cloud Native Database Management System</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/introducing-kubedb-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/introducing-kubedb-enterprise/</guid><description>SAN LEANDRO, Calif. &amp;ndash; AppsCode, a global leader in Enterprise-grade Kubernetes-native Data Platforms, has released KubeDB Enterprise Edition, a production-grade cloud-native database management solution for Kubernetes. KubeDB Enterprise edition is the open core version of popular open source project KubeDB. It includes all the features (clustering, etc.) of KubeDB Community Edition and extends it by automating Day 2 DBA tasks, such as database backup/recovery, upgrading version, horizontal and vertical scaling, TLS/SSL support, updating configuration post provisioning, connection pooling, etc.</description></item><item><title>KubeDB v2021.03.17- Introducing MariaDB and Re-designed PostgreSQL operator</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/kubedb-v2021.03.17/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/kubedb-v2021.03.17/</guid><description>We are pleased to announce KubeDB v2021.03.17. This post lists all the major changes done in this release since v2021.01.26. This release offers MariaDB support with Galera Clustering, Backup and Recovery, TLS and many more features. It also contains the fix for the PostgreSQL data loss issue. The support for the PostgreSQL TLS configuration and the support for official TimescaleDB images has also been added to this release.
MariaDB We are very excited to announce that MariaDB support has been added to KubeDB.</description></item></channel></rss>