<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Emruz Hossain on ByteBuilders Blog</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/authors/emruz-hossain/</link><description>Recent content in Emruz Hossain on ByteBuilders Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.byte.builders/authors/emruz-hossain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stash v2021.03.17 - A Better User Experience</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/stash-v2021.03.17/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/stash-v2021.03.17/</guid><description>We are very excited to announce Stash v2021.03.17. In this release, we have focused on improving the user experience with Stash. We have simplified the installation process, improved KubeDB integration, added backup support for TLS secured databases, etc. We have also fixed various bugs and made other improvements.
In this post, we are going to highlight the major changes. You can find the complete changelog here.
Simplified Installation Process Previously, we had two separate charts for the community edition ( stash-community) and enterprise edition (stash-enterprise).</description></item><item><title>Stash - Introducing Stash Enterprise Edition</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/stash-v2020.08.27/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/stash-v2020.08.27/</guid><description>Update 2020/09/21: Since we published this post, we have received feedback from our existing users. Based on their feedback, we have decided to reconsider the earlier decision. Going forward the Community Edition will include the core backup/recovery functionalities and be available for anyone to use for any purposes including commercial purposes under a new AppsCode Community License. The Enterprise Edition comes with 4 different pricing plans, as described here: https://stash.run/pricing/ .</description></item><item><title>Stash v0.9.0-rc.4 - Introducing Batch Backup and Hooks</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/stash-v0.9.0-rc.4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/stash-v0.9.0-rc.4/</guid><description>We are very excited to announce Stash v0.9.0-rc.4 which brings some cool features like batch backup and hooks. We have also added Percona-XtraDB addon. This version also comes with some bug fixes and general improvements.
Stash by AppsCode is a data backup and recovery solution for Kubernetes workloads. If you are running production workloads in Kubernetes, you might want to take backup of your disks, databases etc. Traditional tools are too complex to setup and maintain in a dynamic compute environment like Kubernetes.</description></item></channel></rss>