<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kubernetes on ByteBuilders Blog</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/tags/kubernetes/</link><description>Recent content in kubernetes on ByteBuilders Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.byte.builders/tags/kubernetes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The case for AppBinding</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/appbinding/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/appbinding/</guid><description>Kubernetes has become the de-facto orchestrator for the cloud native world. Kubernetes upholds the philosophy that the core should be small and allow developers to write their own extensions. One way to introduce new resource types is using CustomResourceDefintions (CRD) (originally known as ThirdPartyResources). Using CRDs anyone can define a new resource type that behaves like standard Kubernetes resources. This allows anyone to write a controller for custom resources and capture operational knowledge in a software form.</description></item><item><title>Secure Kubernetes using eBPF &amp; Open Policy Agent</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/bpf-opa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/bpf-opa/</guid><description>Securing Kubernetes cluster is a multi-faceted task. Runtime security is one aspect of it. It ensures that the workloads deployed in the cluster doesn&amp;rsquo;t do any malicious behaviors. For runtime instrumentation, we wanted to use Extended Berkeley Packet Filter (eBPF), a core technology in the Linux kernel.
There are already many tools available in this space, but each project has its own custom components. We want to use a set of common set of tools and techniques for binding these different components.</description></item><item><title>Kubeform - Provision cloud resources using CRDs &amp; Terraform</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/introducing-kubeform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/introducing-kubeform/</guid><description>Kubeform by AppsCode is a Kubernetes operator for Terraform. Kubeform provides auto-generated Kubernetes CRDs for Terraform resources and modules so that you can manage any cloud infrastructure in a Kubernetes native way. You just write a CRD for a cloud infrastructure, apply it and Kubeform will create it for you! Kubeform currently supports 5 top cloud platforms. These are AWS, Google Cloud, Azure, Digitalocean and Linode.
The key features of Kubeform are:</description></item><item><title>Introducing ResourceDescriptor: A Generic API for defining Kubernetes Resource Graph</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/resourcedescriptor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/resourcedescriptor/</guid><description>Kubernetes has own the container orchestrator war. One of the key contributors to its success is the ability to extend Kubernetes by the end users. The primary way users extend Kubernetes is by defining new resource types. This is called Custom Resource Definitions (CRD) in the Kubernetes parlance. Users can write a controller that can reconcile users&amp;rsquo; desired specification to a cluster. Controllers that capture operational knowledge of a software application are commonly know as Kubernetes operators.</description></item><item><title>KubeVault v0.3.0 - Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/kubevault-v0.3.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/kubevault-v0.3.0/</guid><description>KubeVault is a Kubernetes operator for HashiCorp Vault. Vault is a tool for secrets management, encryption as a service, and privileged access management. Deploying, maintaining, and managing Vault in Kubernetes could be challenging. KubeVault operator makes it easy to deploy, maintain and manage Vault servers in Kubernetes. It covers automatic initialization and unsealing, and securely stores unseal keys and root tokens in a cloud KMS (Key Management Service) service. KubeVault operator eases these operational tasks so that developers can focus on solving business problems.</description></item><item><title>Stash v0.9.0-rc.4 - Introducing Batch Backup and Hooks</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/stash-v0.9.0-rc.4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/stash-v0.9.0-rc.4/</guid><description>We are very excited to announce Stash v0.9.0-rc.4 which brings some cool features like batch backup and hooks. We have also added Percona-XtraDB addon. This version also comes with some bug fixes and general improvements.
Stash by AppsCode is a data backup and recovery solution for Kubernetes workloads. If you are running production workloads in Kubernetes, you might want to take backup of your disks, databases etc. Traditional tools are too complex to setup and maintain in a dynamic compute environment like Kubernetes.</description></item></channel></rss>