<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Md Kamol Hasan on ByteBuilders Blog</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/authors/md-kamol-hasan/</link><description>Recent content in Md Kamol Hasan on ByteBuilders Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.byte.builders/authors/md-kamol-hasan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>KubeVault v0.3.0 - Tools for running HashiCorp Vault on Kubernetes</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/kubevault-v0.3.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/kubevault-v0.3.0/</guid><description>KubeVault is a Kubernetes operator for HashiCorp Vault. Vault is a tool for secrets management, encryption as a service, and privileged access management. Deploying, maintaining, and managing Vault in Kubernetes could be challenging. KubeVault operator makes it easy to deploy, maintain and manage Vault servers in Kubernetes. It covers automatic initialization and unsealing, and securely stores unseal keys and root tokens in a cloud KMS (Key Management Service) service. KubeVault operator eases these operational tasks so that developers can focus on solving business problems.</description></item><item><title>KubeDB v2021.03.17- Introducing MariaDB and Re-designed PostgreSQL operator</title><link>https://blog.byte.builders/post/kubedb-v2021.03.17/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.byte.builders/post/kubedb-v2021.03.17/</guid><description>We are pleased to announce KubeDB v2021.03.17. This post lists all the major changes done in this release since v2021.01.26. This release offers MariaDB support with Galera Clustering, Backup and Recovery, TLS and many more features. It also contains the fix for the PostgreSQL data loss issue. The support for the PostgreSQL TLS configuration and the support for official TimescaleDB images has also been added to this release.
MariaDB We are very excited to announce that MariaDB support has been added to KubeDB.</description></item></channel></rss>